

• 925 Crest Drive Cary, Illinois 60013

T: 847.927.1395

E: Hopkins511@yahoo.com

W: www.roberthopkinsdesign.com



WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR DIGITAL DESIGNER - ALLCAMPUS 2020 - PRESENT

Leading key projects, initiatives and client launches. Design and develop a wide range of collateral for leading universities such as microsites, landing pages, marketing/social media banners, email marketing, brochures and A/B testing.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER & WEB DESIGNER - L2 INTERACTIVE 2006 - 2020

Lead designer for web design concepts, email marketing, microsites and banner ads. In 2016, I was promoted to front-end developer which includes producing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and content management for Corporate and Performing Arts clients.

INTERN - NORTHERN ILLINOIS OUTREACH 2006

Designing print marketing materials such as direct mailers and brochures for the university.



EDUCATION

NORTHERN ILLINOIS UNIVERSITY 2003 - 2006

Bachelor of Fine Arts Degree in Visual Communication

HARPER COLLEGE 2000 - 2002

Associates Degree in Art



REFERENCES

JANA YOUNG

Vice President L2 Interactive 630.677.3853 jana@lynch2.com

LINDSAY MURPHY

PHP Developer Camping World 815.494.0563 linzswanson@gmail.com

DENNIS BASCH

Graphic Designer L2 Interactive 847.772.0419 dennisbasch@yahoo.com

STUART HOPKINS

Web Engineer ActiveCampaign 630.248.8376 stuart.g.hopkins@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

I am a Senior Digital Designer at AllCampus. My primary roles at AllCampus include leading key projects, initiatives and client launches. Design and develop a wide range of collateral for leading universities such as microsites, landing pages, marketing/social media banners, email marketing, brochures and A/B testing. I have been in the web industry for 16 years. Early in my career, I was the lead web designer and front-end developer for L2 Interactive which includes producing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and content management for Corporate and Performing Arts companies.



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

WordPress

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Digital Marketing



EXPERIENCE

80% 100% 80% Seront-End Web WordPress

Design



Development

Industry

Experience



User Experience Ma

Email Marketing